<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8' standalone='no'?>
<doxygen xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="compound.xsd" version="1.8.17">
  <compounddef id="md__home__fy_s__project__fy_s_docs_services_arena__arena__turn_priority_list" kind="page">
    <compoundname>md__home_FyS_Project_FyS_docs_services_arena_Arena_TurnPriorityList</compoundname>
    <title>Turn per Turn priority</title>
    <briefdescription>
    </briefdescription>
    <detaileddescription>
<para><heading level="1">Requirements</heading>
</para>
<para><itemizedlist>
<listitem><para>A full turn is defined as follow: The slowest pit participant played sign the completion of the current turn</para>
</listitem><listitem><para>A player&apos;s character (or a contender) can have multiple action in a single turn depending to its speed</para>
</listitem><listitem><para>The priority list has to be recalculated when :<itemizedlist>
<listitem><para>A player&apos;s character (or contender) die and is temporarily (for player&apos;s character) or definitely removed from the priority list.</para>
</listitem><listitem><para>When a player or a contender join the fight (as for character reviving)</para>
</listitem><listitem><para>The speed of a character has been impacted (by a spell, an item, an attack).</para>
</listitem></itemizedlist>
</para>
</listitem></itemizedlist>
</para>
<para><heading level="1">Implementation</heading>
</para>
<para>Each pit participant has a speed defined as an unsigned integer. The faster go before the slowest. <linebreak/>
</para>
<para><bold>Generation of priorityList</bold> :<orderedlist>
<listitem><para>Order the list of speed from fastest to slowest.</para>
</listitem><listitem><para>The first one is the first one to have a turn (add him in the priority list as first)</para>
</listitem><listitem><para>Subtract his speed with the second one</para>
</listitem><listitem><para>Re-order the list of speed from fastest to slowest.</para>
</listitem><listitem><para>The first one in this list is added in priority list</para>
</listitem><listitem><para>Subtract his speed with the second one</para>
</listitem><listitem><para>Re-order..</para>
</listitem><listitem><para>...</para>
</listitem></orderedlist>
</para>
<para><emphasis>Graphical example</emphasis>, each color represent a different character (monster or player&apos;s character):</para>
<para><image type="html" name="Turn1.png" inline="yes"></image>
</para>
<para>The difference of speed between the fastest and the slowest being important, the purple player can play 4 times before the end of the turn. <linebreak/>
 For the second turn, the base maximum speed is added to the every one plus their own base speed.</para>
<para><image type="html" name="Turn2.png" inline="yes"></image>
</para>
<para>This turn is way shorter than the previous turn (every character play only once), but the next one as the speed stabilized a little bit, but in the third turn, as the purple player end this turn with 19 of speed, he will play multiple times before the end of the turn. <linebreak/>
 This algorithm give an edge to the fast player without being broken (playing multiple time every single turns). <linebreak/>
</para>
<para>Here a resume of the two turns:</para>
<para><image type="html" name="TurnResume.png" inline="yes"></image>
 </para>
    </detaileddescription>
  </compounddef>
</doxygen>
