<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8' standalone='no'?>
<doxygen xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="compound.xsd" version="1.8.17">
  <compounddef id="md__story_plot" kind="page">
    <compoundname>md_StoryPlot</compoundname>
    <title>FreeYourSoul</title>
    <briefdescription>
    </briefdescription>
    <detaileddescription>
<para><heading level="1">Factions:</heading>
</para>
<para><itemizedlist>
<listitem><para>Renegades</para>
</listitem><listitem><para>Guardians</para>
</listitem><listitem><para>Empire</para>
</listitem></itemizedlist>
</para>
<para><heading level="1">Introduction</heading>
</para>
<para>Welcome to Amerite</para>
<para><image type="html" name="Ameritte.jpg" inline="yes"></image>
</para>
<para>Long time ago, goddess was walking along humans, living on the Vakoh, a floating island with a worshipping people, the Guardians while the other humans stayed living below. Granting them favor for their fidelity, they wanted to keep this people by their side. To do so, they shackled their soul into their body in order for them to not be able to die and called them Guardians of Vakoh, with the hope of the guardians worshipping them forever. But the goddesses didn&apos;t bother ask the permission to do such thing, which irritated some of their followers, whom centuries after centuries living, felt the feeling of wanting more. The Goddesses accepted granting a favor to them, and decided to land Vakoh, the holy island, in the great sea, in order to let the Guardians live aside with the other normal humans. Centuries passed, and the irritation of some Guardians towards their immortality progressed into hatred. Living side by side with their humans peer made them realize how lonely they were. Seeing loved one leave while they felt trapped on earth. They started calling their divine gift a curse. They asked the goddess to release the soul bounding spell. The Goddess refused as they grew attached to all of their followers. The fidel Guardians didn&apos;t approve and forgive such a disrespectful request and decided to exile them, and renamed them Renegades. <linebreak/>
 Having to quit the holy island and their goddess protection, they decided to continue living with the humans.</para>
<para>The greed and jealousy of the humans realm combined with the hatred of the Renegades started the holy war. Endless fight between Guardians and Renegades, endless slaughter between humans, mortal believer against immortality seeker of the Empire. Disgusted by those reactions and the acts human perpetuated, the goddess decided to leave the human realm, letting them fight over. <linebreak/>
 After 5 years of battle, a truce is made between the Guardians being over-numbered, suffering from capture and torture despite not being able to die, and humans counting countless dead.</para>
<para>A pact is made, the Guardians returned in the holy island and shared some of their knowledge about souls given by the Goddess in order to quench the greed of the humans. The Renegades taken as responsible of the war and departure of the Goddess, didn&apos;t have the right to go back to Vakoh and had to live further in the mountains, still looking for a way to release themselves from their own bodies. </para>
    </detaileddescription>
  </compounddef>
</doxygen>
